let questions29 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "to advertise",
        answer: "A. werben",
        options: [
            "A. werben",
            "B. kaufen",
            "C. planen",
            "D. bauen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "to assign",
        answer: "B. zuweisen",
        options: [
            "A. ablehnen",
            "B. zuweisen",
            "C. beenden",
            "D. vergessen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "audience",
        answer: "C. Publikum",
        options: [
            "A. Schauspieler",
            "B. Wettbewerb",
            "C. Publikum",
            "D. Trainer"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "breakfast",
        answer: "A. Frühstück",
        options: [
            "A. Frühstück",
            "B. Mittagessen",
            "C. Abendessen",
            "D. Snack"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "competition",
        answer: "D. Wettbewerb",
        options: [
            "A. Training",
            "B. Zuschauer",
            "C. Herausforderung",
            "D. Wettbewerb"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "cool",
        answer: "B. kühl",
        options: [
            "A. heiß",
            "B. kühl",
            "C. warm",
            "D. trocken"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "to gain",
        answer: "A. gewinnen",
        options: [
            "A. gewinnen",
            "B. verlieren",
            "C. vermeiden",
            "D. vernachlässigen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "importance",
        answer: "C. Bedeutung",
        options: [
            "A. Reichtum",
            "B. Spaß",
            "C. Bedeutung",
            "D. Freude"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "knowledge",
        answer: "A. Wissen",
        options: [
            "A. Wissen",
            "B. Stärke",
            "C. Schwäche",
            "D. Gedächtnis"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "major",
        answer: "D. groß",
        options: [
            "A. klein",
            "B. unwichtig",
            "C. einfach",
            "D. groß"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "mean",
        answer: "C. gemein",
        options: [
            "A. freundlich",
            "B. glücklich",
            "C. gemein",
            "D. traurig"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "to prefer",
        answer: "A. bevorzugen",
        options: [
            "A. bevorzugen",
            "B. ablehnen",
            "C. vergessen",
            "D. ignorieren"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "president",
        answer: "B. Präsident",
        options: [
            "A. Schüler",
            "B. Präsident",
            "C. Lehrer",
            "D. Freund"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "progress",
        answer: "C. Fortschritt",
        options: [
            "A. Rückschritt",
            "B. Misserfolg",
            "C. Fortschritt",
            "D. Stillstand"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "respect",
        answer: "A. Respekt",
        options: [
            "A. Respekt",
            "B. Verachtung",
            "C. Gleichgültigkeit",
            "D. Abneigung"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "rich",
        answer: "B. reich",
        options: [
            "A. arm",
            "B. reich",
            "C. sparsam",
            "D. großzügig"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "skill",
        answer: "A. Fähigkeit",
        options: [
            "A. Fähigkeit",
            "B. Ahnungslosigkeit",
            "C. Zufall",
            "D. Pech"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "somehow",
        answer: "C. irgendwie",
        options: [
            "A. sicher",
            "B. definitiv",
            "C. irgendwie",
            "D. genau"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "strength",
        answer: "B. Stärke",
        options: [
            "A. Schwäche",
            "B. Stärke",
            "C. Anfälligkeit",
            "D. Zärtlichkeit"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "to vote",
        answer: "A. wählen",
        options: [
            "A. wählen",
            "B. ignorieren",
            "C. ablehnen",
            "D. verlassen"
        ]
    }
];
